[
  {
    "question": "What kind of experience are you looking for?",
    "answer": "Levels of Sweetness",
    "counter": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of sweetness are you looking for?",
    "answer": "Tropical & Exotic Sweetness",
    "counter": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you think of pineapple?",
    "answer": "Love it!",
    "counter": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you in the mood for?",
    "answer": "Fruity Gin-based Cocktail",
    "counter": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you in the mood for?",
    "answer": "Bubbling spritz with melon",
    "counter": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you think of pineapple?",
    "answer": "Not a fan",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you in the mood for?",
    "answer": "Rum-classic with a twist",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you in the mood for?",
    "answer": "Bubbling spritz with Banana",
    "counter": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of sweetness are you looking for?",
    "answer": "Berry-Focused Sweetness",
    "counter": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s your guilty pleasure?",
    "answer": "Strawberry-Dominant",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s your guilty pleasure?",
    "answer": "Raspberries & Passion Fruit",
    "counter": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of sweetness are you looking for?",
    "answer": "Rich & Sweet",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s your go-to booze?",
    "answer": "Rum",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s your go-to booze?",
    "answer": "Masticha",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s your go-to booze?",
    "answer": "Tequila",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of experience are you looking for?",
    "answer": "Light and Refreshing",
    "counter": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is your preferred spirit base?",
    "answer": "Gin",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What is your preferred spirit base?",
    "answer": "Prosecco",
    "counter": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fruit flavor do you prefer?",
    "answer": "Peach-Flavored",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fruit flavor do you prefer?",
    "answer": "Banana-Flavored",
    "counter": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is your preferred spirit base?",
    "answer": "Moschato D'asti",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What excites your taste buds?",
    "answer": "Strawberry Delight",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What excites your taste buds?",
    "answer": "Tropical Vibe",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of experience are you looking for?",
    "answer": "Bold and Complex",
    "counter": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What flavor complexity excites you?",
    "answer": "Classics with a twist",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s your combo?",
    "answer": "Gin-Infused and Bitter",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s your combo?",
    "answer": "Rum-based with tropical sweetness",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What flavor complexity excites you?",
    "answer": "Smokey & Spicy",
    "counter": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s your signature duo?",
    "answer": "Spicy with Tequila",
    "counter": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s your signature duo?",
    "answer": "Bitter-Sweet and Smokey",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What flavor complexity excites you?",
    "answer": "Sweet Meets Salty",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Feeling adventurous?",
    "answer": "Yes, surprise me!",
    "counter": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Feeling adventurous?",
    "answer": "No, keep it simple",
    "counter": 0
  }
]